I got it up to 450 watts.
Here a 250-watt lamp and 200 watts is burning.
Here it is, this contraption.
And this lamp, like Akula's, I bought too.
In short, well, here it is.
Here's the little oscilloscope trace.
Here, the consumption is now 24 volts.
Here, we look at the power supply.
Here it is.
It's fed from the power supply.
The generator works.
Strange that you absolutely have to hook it to the ground here, otherwise it doesn't work.
And it also starts up rather with difficulty.
What do we have here.
This is the high-voltage power for this contraption.
And here's the output on the bulb.
Oh, the wire went.
Here it is.
And, in short, here.
It's burning.
But for now I'm not very happy with the result.
First, it squeals.
But it squeals, fine, to hell with it.
I'll unwind this transformer a bit now.
I need more here.
And I think the idea with the nanosecond gen is a crappy one.
Somehow I want to slam a Tesla in here.
Well, we'll see.